<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- Author: -->
<aiml>
  <category>
    <pattern>I WOULD LIKE HELP WITH *</pattern>
    <template>
      <think>
        <set name ="userFinanceChoice">
          <star/>
        </set>
      </think>
      <condition name="userFinanceChoice">
        <li value="financial support">There are a few financial matters that I can help with. Government support, and local council support. What type of support are you looking for?</li>
        <li>I'm sorry, I didn't catch that, Could you repeat?</li>
      </condition>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>Could I get help with *</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>I WOULD LIKE HELP WITH</srai>
      <srai>
        <star/>
      </srai>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>Please could you help me with *</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>I WOULD LIKE HELP WITH</srai>
      <srai>
        <star/>
      </srai>
    </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <pattern>Government support</pattern>
    <template>
      In terms of government support, they are able to provide universal credit to whoever meets the requirements. Would you like to learn more about the requirements for universal credit?
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>MORE UNIVERSAL CREDIT HELP</pattern>
    <template>
      To apply for universal credit, there are a few conditions which will be listed below:
      - You must live in the UK. 
      - You must be older than 18 years old, but there are however a couple of exceptions.
      - You must be under the state pension age. 
      - You must have £16,000 or less in money, savings and investments.
      - You may make claims for support depending on health conditions or disabilities. To find out more regarding disabilities, please follow this link: https://www.gov.uk/health-conditions-disability-universal-credit.
      - For under 18s, there are a few other conditions that apply, if you would like to know please specify below.
    </template>  
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>universal credit</pattern>
      <template>
        <srai>MORE UNIVERSAL CREDIT HELP</srai>
      </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>YES</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>MORE UNIVERSAL CREDIT HELP</srai>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>okay</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>MORE UNIVERSAL CREDIT HELP</srai>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>ok</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>MORE UNIVERSAL CREDIT HELP</srai>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>yes please</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>MORE UNIVERSAL CREDIT HELP</srai>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>UNDER 18</pattern>
    <template>
      To apply for universal credit under the age of 18 any of the following conditions must apply:
      - You have a health condition or disability and have medical evidence for it, such as a fit note. 
      - You are caring for a severely disabled person. 
      - You are responsible for a child. 
      - You live with your partner, have a child, and your partner is eligible for unviersal credit.
      - You are pregnant and expecting your baby in the next 11 weeks. 
      - You have had a baby in the last 15 weeks. 
      - You do not have parental support, you do not live with your parents and are not under local authority care. 
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>I am under 18</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>UNDER 18</srai>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>support for under 18</pattern>
    <template>
      <srai>UNDER 18</srai>
    </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <pattern>LOCAL COUNCIL SUPPORT</pattern>
    <template>
      The local council may offer housing benefits to anyone who satisfies the following conditions:
      - You may claim for housing benefits if you rent from a private landlord or letting agency. 
      - You rent from a housing association.
      - You rent from a charity.
      - Or you rent from the council itself.
      You are entitled to claim council tax support even if you own your home, but you won't be able to claim housing benefit.
      To learn more, please follow this link: https://exeter.gov.uk/benefits-and-welfare/how-to-claim-benefits/what-you-need-to-know-about-benefits/benefit-support-available/
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>HELP WITH MONEY SAVING</pattern>
    <template>
      One of the most frequent tips given for money saving around the house is to have your insulation checked. 
      A lot of homes are poorly insulated and lose a lot of heat through the walls and roof. 
      Certain companies offer a free consultation/check up on your house.
      Get more energy efficient appliances.
      More efficient light bulbs.
      One long term and quite expensive idea is to install your own solar panels which will reduce the amount of energy you will need to buy from energy companies.
    </template>
  </category>
</aiml>