<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<aiml>
	<!-- Code for the topic functions, and information regarding what topics the bot covers. -->
	
	<!-- Discuss. -->

	<category>
		<pattern>DISCUSS *</pattern>
		<template>
			<think><set name = "discuss"><star/></set></think>
			<condition name = "discuss">
				<li value = "means tested"><think><set name = "topic">means tested</set></think>
					What would you like to know about means-tested financial support?</li>			
				<li value = "energy companies"><think><set name ="topic">energy companies</set></think>
					What would you like to know about financial support from energy companies via the government?</li>			
				<li value = "council support">
					What would you like to know about financial support from the <set name = "topic">council</set>?</li>
				<li value = "electricity">
					What would you like to know about money saving tips for the home regarding <set name = "topic">electricity</set> usage?</li>
				<li value ="gas">
					What would you like to know about money saving tips for the home regarding <set name = "topic">gas</set> usage?</li>
				<li value = "further advice">
					What would you like to know about where to go for further <set name = "topic">advice</set>?</li>
				<li>"<get name ="discuss"/>" is not a topic I know. Please type "what do you know" to see what topics I can talk about</li>
			</condition>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	
	<!-- Telling the user what the current topic is when asked. -->
	
	<category>
		<pattern>WHAT IS THE TOPIC</pattern>
		<template>
			<condition name = "topic">
				<li value = "means tested">We are currently discussing means tested financial support</li>
				<li value = "energy companies">We are currently discussing financial support from energy companies via the government</li>
				<li value = "council">We are currently discussing finincial support from the council</li>
				<li value = "electricity">We are currently discussing money saving tips for the home regarding electricity usage</li>
				<li value = "gas">We are currently discussing money saving tips for the home regarding gas usage</li>
				<li value = "advice">We are currently discussing where to go for further advice</li>
				<li>There is currently no topic set</li>
			</condition>
		</template>
	</category>

	<category>
		<pattern>what are * talking about</pattern>
		<template>
			<srai>WHAT IS THE TOPIC</srai>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>what are * discussing</pattern>
		<template>
			<srai>WHAT IS THE TOPIC</srai>
		</template>
	</category>

	<!-- Telling the user what knowledge the bot has. -->

	<category>
		<pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW</pattern>
		<template>
			I was created to provide advice to people regarding how to save living costs, and how to apply for government and council support.
The topics I can talk about are:
MEANS TESTED financial support
Financial support from ENERGY COMPANIES via the government
Financial COUNCIL SUPPORT
Money saving tips for the home regarding ELECTRICITY usage
Money saving tips for the home regarding GAS usage
Where to go for FURTHER ADVICE

To choose a topic, type "discuss" followed by one of the above capitalised phrases.
For example, type "discuss means tested" to choose to talk about means-tested financial support
		</template>
	</category>
</aiml>